Guide to the Stuart Sherman Papers 1945-2001 (Bulk 1961-2001) MSS 192
© 2009 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Artwork
  - Collage works, 1995-1996 (Box 5A, Folder 124)
  - Collage works, 1995-1997 (Box 5A, Folder 125)
  - Collage works, 1995-1997 (Box 5A, Folder 126)
  - Collage works - "Book of Colors", 1/25/96, 1995-1996 (Box 5A, Folder 127)
  - Collage works - "Asses to Asses" [orig. housed in binder], 1996 (Box 5A, Folder 128)
  - Collage works - [orig. housed in binder], 1996-1997 (Box 5A, Folder 129)
  - Collage works - w/ exhibition sign, May 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 5A, Folder 130)
  - Collage works, 1999 (Box 5A, Folder 131)
  - Collage works, drawings, notes, poetry - 2/01-7/01, 2001 (Box 5A, Folder 132)
  - Collage works and drawing, undated (Box 5A, Folder 133)
  - Paper sculpture/collage, undated (Box 5A, Folder 134)
- Series VII: Photographs
  This series contains all photo materials including negative, contact sheets, and photographs.
  - Photographs and Negatives - "Stations of the Cross, or the Passion of Stuart", [2001] (Box 6 (photo binder), Folder 12 sleeves)
  - Photographs - "Stations of the Cross, or the Passion of Stuart"; photographer: Herman Sorgeloos, 2001 (Box 6 (photo binder), Folder 3 sleeves)
  - Photographs - "Perfilmance", Anthology Film Archives, 11/5/94; photographer: Larry Miller, 1994 (Box 6 (photo binder), Folder 2 sleeves)
  - Photographs and Negatives - [shoes] with note from photographer: Tim Balderstone, 1984 (Box 6 (photo binder), Folder 11 sleeves)
  - Contact Sheets - "Room Enough?", 12/30/77; photographer: Nathaniel Tileston, 1977 (Box 6 (photo binder), Folder 2 sleeves)
  - Photographs and Negatives - Misc performance, Sculpture, Promotional, etc.; photographers incl. Babette Mangolte, Netty A Mamahit, Christian Blei, et al, undated (Box 6 (photo binder), Folder 39 sleeves)
  - Photographs and Negatives - Misc. personal, family, etc., undated (Box 6 (photo binder), Folder 8 sleeves)
  - Photographs w/ cardboard frame - Parents, 1972 (Box 6 (photo binder), Folder 2 sleeves)
  - Photograph w/ cardboard frame - unidentified event, undated (Box 6 (photo binder), Folder 2 sleeves)
- Series VIII: Slides
  This series contains all slides from the Stuart Sherman Papers.
  - Slides - Misc. Performance, Exhibit, etc., undated (Box 7 (slide binder), Folder 24 sleeves)
  - Slides - Misc. Performance, Exhibit, etc., undated (Box 8 (slide binder), Folder 21 sleeves)
- Series IX: Video
  Scope and Content note
  This series contains the videotaped material from the Stuart Sherman Papers. Researcher access is limited to Subseries A: Video Recordings - Access Copies.
  - Subseries A: Video Recordings - Access Copies
    - Selections from "The First Spectacle" (perf. on the set of R. Foreman's "Pandering to the Masses"), 4/75, 1975 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0220)
      General note
      Format: DVD
      TRT: 00:26:46
      Source ID: 192.0155
      Original Format: U-matic
    - Selections from Spectacles, 1975-1976 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0388)
      TRT: [00:15:00]
      Source ID: 192.0147
    - "The Second Spectacle" (w/ Stefan Brecht, Richard Foreman, Kate Manheim), [197-] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0217)
      TRT: 00:45:00
      Source ID: 192.0154
    - Segment from "Sunday" cable tv program, 06/76; pre-production perf.; discussion w/ Jerald Ordover, 1976 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0253)
      TRT: 00:23:37
      Source ID: 192.0034
    - "The Seventh Spectacle", [1976] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0406)
      TRT: [00:00:00]
      Source ID: 192.0158
    - Selections from Films ("Scotty and Stuart", "Skating", "Flying") and Performances ("11th and 10th Spectacles", "Hamlet", "Oedipus", "Faust", "Chekhov", "Strindberg", "Brecht"), [1977-1986] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0340)
      TRT: 00:35:00
      Source ID: 192.0141
    - Compilation Tape - selections from Films ("Scotty and Stuart", "Skating", "Flying") and Performances ("11th Spectacle", "10th Spectacle", "Hamlet", "Oedipus", "Faust", "Chekhov"), [1977-1986] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0373)
      TRT: [00:24:00]
      Source ID: 192.0138
    - Excerpts from "The Classical Trilogy (Hamlet, Oedipus, Faust)" and "The Second Trilogy (Chekhov, Strindberg, Brecht)", [1977-1986] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0397)
      Source ID: 192.0152
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)" and "Portrait of Stuart Sherman" (from "The Eighth Spectacle"), [1979] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0277)
      TRT: 00:20:25
      Source ID: 192.0060
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)" and "Portrait of Stuart Sherman" (from "The Eighth Spectacle"), [1979] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0283)
      TRT: 00:20:00
      Source ID: 192.0062
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)" and "Portrait of Stuart Sherman" (from "The Eighth Spectacle"), [1979] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0295)
      TRT: 00:22:11
      Source ID: 192.0067
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)" and "Portrait of Stuart Sherman" (from "The Eighth Spectacle"), [1979] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0400)
      TRT: [00:20:00]
      Source ID: 192.0156
    - 4 videos - "Berlin…" (1986), "Gray Matter" (1987), "Video Walk" (1987), "Five Flowers" (1979), 1979, 1986, 1987 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0361)
      TRT: [00:09:00]
      Source ID: 192.0076
    - "The Thirteenth Spectacle (Language)", 10/17/80, 1980 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0244)
      TRT: 00:38:00
      Source ID: 192.0162
      Original Format: Betamax
    - Tape 1, Language [?], 11/9/80; original unedited material (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0334)
      Source ID: 192.0133A
    - Tape 2, 11/9/80 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0385)
      Source ID: 192.0146
    - "The Tenth Spectacle" - Toulouse Lyon (take 2), St. Petersburg (3), NY (2), Woonsocket (1), Amsterdam (1), Mexico City (1), Woonsochet (2), 1980 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0370)
      Source ID: 192.0137
    - "The Tenth Spectacle", [1980] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0403)
      Source ID: 192.0157
    - "The Twelfth Spectacle (Language)", 1981 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0409)
      Source ID: 192.0160
    - "The Twelfth Spectacle (Language)", [1981] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0364)
      TRT: [00:30:00]
      Source ID: 192.0126
    - "Faust - A Portrait by Stuart Sherman", Theater Am Turm, Frankfurt, [1981-1984] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0250)
      TRT: 00:22:08
      Source ID: 192.0033
    - "Faust" (camera: Lisa), [1981-1984] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0301)
      TRT: 00:03:44
      Source ID: 192.0031
    - "Faust" (New Approach; camera 2, tape 2), [1981-1984] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0259)
      TRT: 00:22:22
      Source ID: 192.0053
    - "Faust" #2, MCAD (close-up table, close-up film), [1981-1984] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0298)
      TRT: 00:08:38
      Source ID: 192.0068
    - "Oedipus", [1981-1984] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0367)
      Source ID: 192.0129
    - "Oedipus" #1, MCAD (camera 3), [1981-1984] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0292)
      TRT: 00:20:36
      Source ID: 192.0065
    - "Hamlet, a portrait", [1981-1984] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0391)
      TRT: [00:25:00]
      Source ID: 192.0149
    - "Hamlet" (tape 2), [1981-1984] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0265)
      TRT: 00:22:25
      Source ID: 192.0056
    - "Hamlet" (unedited), Tape 5[?] pre-shoot for June 12, [1981-1984] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0289)
      TRT: 00:22:20
      Source ID: 192.0064
    - "Five Flowers", [1982] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0322)
      TRT: 00:02:00
    - Performance "Mat. Fac." [?], 10/30/83, 1983 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0394)
      Source ID: 192.0151
    - MIT Hallway [1984/5], 1984-1985 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0412)
      General Note
      TRT: 00:24:00
    - "21 Films", 1984 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0349)
      TRT: 00:50:00
      Source ID: 192.0159
    - "Faust" #1, MCAD (close-up table w/ globes; side shot w/ interruptions; wide shot #2), [1984] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0247)
      TRT: 00:22:03
      Source ID: 192.0032
    - MIT, [1984/5] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0337)
      TRT: 00:07:00
      Source ID: 192.0140
    - "Chekhov", MIT (video by Glorianna Davenport/Steve Keuttel), [1984/5] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0358)
      Source ID: 192.0073
    - "Inside/Outside (Inside an Outsider's View of MIT)", MIT, 3/85, 1985 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0256)
      TRT: 00:22:41
      Source ID: 192.0051
    - "Trilogy" - Brecht, The Kitchen, 6/23/86, 1986 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0310)
      TRT: 00:19:55
      Source ID: 192.0071
    - "Trilogy - Chekhov, Strindberg", The Kitchen (High Speed Dub), [1986] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0307)
      TRT: 00:21:00
      Source ID: 192.0070
    - "Berlin (West)/ Andere Richtungen", [1986] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0355)
      TRT: 00:10:00
      Source ID: 192.0125
    - "An Evening of Performance and Film", 6/9/88 (Tape 1 of 2), 1988 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0325)
      Source ID: 192.0130
    - "An Evening of Performance and Film", 6/9/88 (Tape 2 of 2), 1988 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0328)
      Source ID: 192.0131
    - Tape #1 - "SSB, Nancy Tobin, Stalemate, [illegible subtitles], sneezing", [1988] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0271)
      TRT: 00:20:08
      Source ID: 192.0058
    - "The Fourteenth Spectacle", 8/26/89, 1989 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0223)
      TRT: 00:52:48
      Source ID: 192.0161
      Original Format: VHS
    - "Black-Eyed Susan (Portrait of An Actress)", 1989 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0382)
      TRT: [00:11:00]
      Source ID: 192.0144
    - "Tea" (A intro), [1989] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0376)
      Source ID: 192.0142
    - "Tea" (B), [1989] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0316)
      TRT: 01:04:13
      Source ID: 192.0075
    - "Tea" (intro of B+C [?]), [1989] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0319)
      TRT: 00:51:00
      Source ID: 192.0127
    - "Tea" (C), [1989] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0343)
      Source ID: 192.0145
    - "The Fifteenth Spectacle: Epoche," 6/23/90, 1990 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0418)
    - Video Mix, Whitney Museum, 11/25/90, 1990 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0379)
      TRT: [00:13:06]
      Source ID: 192.0143
    - "A Glass of Fish", [1993] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0304)
      TRT: 00:06:45
      Source ID: 192.0069
    - "Liberation (A Portrait of Berenice Reynaud)", [1993] (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0331)
      TRT: 00:08:30
      Source ID: 192.0132
    - "Perfilmance" at Anthology, 11/5/94, 1994 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0313)
      TRT: 01:02:19
      Source ID: 192.0074
    - ["Spectacle" 6/17/97], 1997 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0415)
      TRT: 01:04:00
    - Stuart Sherman segment from KRMA-TV production of "Season Ticket" [interview], undated (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0280)
      Source ID: 192.0061
    - Tape #1 - pre-shoot [unidentified project], undated (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0262)
      TRT: 00:19:09
      Source ID: 192.0055
    - Tape #2 - pre-shoot, June 12, undated (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0274)
      Source ID: 192.0059
    - Tape #2 - original material, [illegible subtitles] "music/ bulls/ mouse", undated (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0286)
      TRT: 00:19:04
      Source ID: 192.0063
    - Tape #3 - "Eyes", undated (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0352)
      TRT: 00:16:05
      Source ID: 192.0052
    - "Forest Fire", undated (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0268)
      TRT: 00:23:08
      Source ID: 192.0057
    - Performance selections, undated (Shelf Media, Media ID: 192.0346)
      Source ID: 192.0150
  - Subseries B: Video Recordings - Originals
    - Performance 8/10/75, 1975 (Folder ID: 192.0038)
      Format: 1/2" video tape
      TRT: [unknown]
    - Selections from "The First Spectacle" (perf. on the set of R. Foreman's "Pandering to the Masses"), 4/75, 1975 (Folder ID: 192.0155)
      Format: U-matic
    - "The First Spectacle", 4/15/75 (Cathy Scott), 1975 (Folder ID: 192.0193)
      Format: 1/2" reel
    - Stuart Sherman's Spectacles - Selections 1975-1976 (Folder ID: 192.0091)
    - Selections from Spectacles, 1975-1976 (Folder ID: 192.0147)
    - "The Second Spectacle" (part 1), [197-] (Folder ID: 192.0041)
    - "The Second Spectacle" (w/ Stefan Brecht, Richard Foreman, Kate Manheim), [197-] (Folder ID: 192.0154)
    - ["The Fourth Spectacle" ?], [197-] (Folder ID: 192.0194)
    - Segment from "Sunday" cable tv program, 06/76; pre-production perf.; discussion w/ Jerald Ordover, 1976 (Folder ID: 192.0034)
    - "The Seventh Spectacle" (with 30 Performers), 1976 (Folder ID: 192.0035)
    - "The Seventh Spectacle" (with 30 Performers), 1976 (Folder ID: 192.0036)
    - "The Seventh Spectacle" (with 30 Performers), [1976] (Folder ID: 192.0158)
    - Compilation Tape - selections from Films ("Scotty and Stuart", "Skating", "Flying") and Performances ("11th and 10th Spectacles", "Hamlet", "Oedipus", "Faust", "Chekhov"), [1977-1986] (Folder ID: 192.0138)
    - Selections from Films ("Scotty and Stuart", "Skating", "Flying") and Performances ("11th and 10th Spectacles", "Hamlet", "Oedipus", "Faust", "Chekhov", "Strindberg", "Brecht"), [1977-1986] (Folder ID: 192.0141)
    - 4 videos - "Berlin…" (1986), "Gray Matter" (1987), "Video Walk" (1987), "Five Flowers" (1979), 1979, 1986, 1987 (Folder ID: 192.0076)
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)", [1979] (Folder ID: 192.0139)
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)"; and "Portrait of Stuart Sherman" from "The Eighth Spectacle", [1979] (Folder ID: 192.0148)
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)" and "Portrait of Stuart Sherman" (from "The Eighth Spectacle"), [1979] (Folder ID: 192.0060)
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)" and "Portrait of Stuart Sherman" (from "The Eighth Spectacle"), [1979] (Folder ID: 192.0062)
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)" and "Portrait of Stuart Sherman" (from "The Eighth Spectacle"), [1979] (Folder ID: 192.0067)
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)" and "Portrait of Stuart Sherman" (from "The Eighth Spectacle"), [1979] (Folder ID: 192.0156)
    - Tape 1, "Language" [?], 11/9/80; original unedited material (Folder 192.0133A)
    - "The Tenth Spectacle" - Coconut Grove FL (take 3), Harper Kansas (4), Cairo (3), Copenhagan (2), London (3), Paris (3), Geneva (2), Amsterdam, Corfn[?] (2), Tokyo Milan (3), San Francisco (2), Istanbul (2), 1980 (Folder ID: 192.0136)
    - "The Tenth Spectacle" - Toulouse Lyon (take 2), St. Petersburg (3), NY (2), Woonsocket (1), Amsterdam (1), Mexico City (1), Woonsochet (2), 1980 (Folder ID: 192.0137)
    - "The Tenth Spectacle", [1980] (Folder ID: 192.0157)
    - Tape 2, 11/9/80 (Folder ID: 192.0146)
    - "The Thirteenth Spectacle (Language)", 10/17/80, 1980 (Folder ID: 192.0162)
      Format: Betamax
      TRT: 0038:00
    - "3=1 (A Careful Misreading)" based on poems by Stefan Brecht, Edwin Denby, Peter Frank; Performers: Mickey Greenall and Fiona Templeton; Mickery Theater, Amsterdam, 1980 (Folder ID: 192.0167)
    - "The Twelfth Spectacle (Language)", 1981 (Folder ID: 192.0160)
    - "The Twelfth Spectacle (Language)", [1981] (Folder ID: 192.0126)
    - "Faust (A Portrait)", Theater Am Turm, Frankfurt, [1981-1984] (Folder ID: 192.0163)
    - "Faust (A Portrait by Stuart Sherman)", Theater Am Turm, Frankfurt, [1981-1984] (Folder ID: 192.0033)
    - "Faust" (camera: Lisa), [981-1984] (Folder ID: 192.0031)
    - "Faust" (New Approach; camera 2, tape 2), [1981-1984] (Folder ID: 192.0053)
    - "Oedipus", [1981-1984] (Folder ID: 192.0128)
    - "Hamlet, a portrait", [1981-1984] (Folder ID: 192.0149)
    - "Hamlet", [1981-1984] (Folder ID: 192.0087)
      Format: VHS
    - "Hamlet", [1981-1984] (Folder ID: 192.0189)
      Format: Hi8
    - "Hamlet" (tape 2), [1981-1984] (Folder ID: 192.0056)
    - "Hamlet" (unedited), Tape 5[?] pre-shoot for June 12, [1981-1984] (Folder ID: 192.0064)
    - Excerpts from "The Classical Trilogy (Hamlet, Oedipus, Faust)" and "The Second Trilogy (Chekhov, Strindberg, Brecht)", [1981-1986] (Folder ID: 192.0152)
    - Excerpts from "The Classical Trilogy (Hamlet, Oedipus, Faust)" and "The Second Trilogy (Chekhov, Strindberg, Brecht)", [1981-1986] (Folder ID: 192.0153)
    - Excerpts from "The Classical Trilogy (Hamlet, Oedipus, Faust)" and "The Second Trilogy (Chekhov, Strindberg, Brecht)", [1981-1986] (Folder ID: 192.0135)
    - "Five Flowers", [1982] (Folder ID: 192.0129)
    - Performance "Mat. Fac." [?], 10/30/83, 1983 (Folder ID: 192.0151)
    - "Theater for New City" [?] (shot by Taka Iimura), 1983 (Folder ID: 192.0170)
    - "Hamlet", MCAD Performance, 4/84, 1984 (Folder ID: 192.0072)
    - "Hamlet", MCAD Performance, 4/84, 1984 (Folder ID: 192.0164)
      TRT: [00:17:00]
    - "Oedipus", MCAD Performance, 4/84, 1984 (Folder ID: 192.0166)
      TRT: [00:18:30]
    - "Oedipus" #1, MCAD (camera 3), [1984] (Folder ID: 192.0065)
    - "Oedipus" #3, MCAD Performance (camera 3), [1984] (Folder ID: 192.0066)
    - "Faust" #1, MCAD (close-up table w/ globes; side shot w/ interruptions; wide shot #2), [1984] (Folder ID: 192.0032)
    - "Faust" #2, MCAD (close-up table, close-up film), [1984] (Folder ID: 192.0068)
    - "21 Films", 1984 (Folder ID: 192.0159)
    - "21 Films", [1984] (Folder ID: 192.0169)
    - MIT Hallway, [1984/5] (Folder ID: 192.0018)
    - MIT, [1984/5] (Folder ID: 192.0140)
    - "Inide/Outside (Inside an Outsider's View of MIT)", MIT, 3/85, 1985 (Folder ID: 192.0051)
    - "Chekhov", MIT, 1985 (Folder ID: 192.0086)
    - "Chekhov", MIT (video by Glorianna Davenport/Steve Keuttel), [1985] (Folder ID: 192.0073)
    - "Chekhov", [1985/6] (Folder ID: 192.0089)
    - "Chekhov", wide angle 2, [1985/6] (Folder ID: 192.0002)
      Format: Betacam
    - "Chekhov", Reel #3, [1985/6] (Folder ID: 192.0003)
    - "Chekhov", Tape #4, [1985/6] (Folder ID: 192.0004)
    - "Chekhov", #5, [1985/6] (Folder ID: 192.0005)
    - "Chekhov", #6, [1985/6] (Folder ID: 192.0006)
    - Interview for "What's On" Cable TV, 1/4/85, 1985 (Folder ID: 192.0165)
    - "TAAL…" plus "Fire!, Fire!"…, [1986, 1990?] (Folder ID: 192.0082)
    - "The Curse of Sentimentality", Central Park Bandshell 8/10/1986 (Folder ID: 192.0007)
      Format: Beta
    - "Curse of…", Summerstage, [1986] (Folder ID: 192.0117)
    - "Berlin (West)/ Andere Richtungen", 1986 (Folder ID: 192.0027)
      TRT: [00:06:00]
    - "Berlin (West)/ Andere Richtungen", [1986] (Folder ID: 192.0125)
    - "Gates of Dawn" 8/15/86, 1986 (Folder ID: 192.0029)
    - "Gates of Dawn", [1986] (Folder ID: 192.0030)
    - "Trilogy - Chekhov, Strindberg", The Kitchen, 6/23/86, 1986 (Folder ID: 192.0168)
    - "Trilogy - Chekhov, Strindberg", The Kitchen (High Speed Dub), [1986] (Folder ID: 192.0070)
    - "Trilogy - Brecht", The Kitchen, 6/23/86, 1986 (Folder ID: 192.0071)
    - "Brecht", [1986] (Folder ID: 192.0015)
    - "Brecht and other performances", [1986] (Folder ID: 192.0083)
    - "Cabaret"/ "One-Night Stands", La MaMa, 6/16/1987, w/ George Ashley, Perrry Greaves, John Hagan, Anne Iobst, Mark Boone Jr., Georg Osterman, Scotty Snyder (Folder ID: 192.0010)
    - "One-Night Stands", La MaMa, 6/16/87, 1987 (Folder ID: 192.0095)
    - "Cabaret", [1987] (Folder ID: 192.0078)
    - HOME, 2/22/87, 1987 (Folder ID: 192.0017)
    - "An Evening of One-Act Plays and 2 Films", HOME for Contemporary Theater and Art, 3/1/87; incl. "Eating", "It is Against the Law...", "The Man in Room 2538", "This House is Mine...", "Endless Meadows...", "The Book and the Window...", "Chatanooga Choo-Choo", "A for Actor", "The Discovery of the Phonograph", 1987 (Folder 192.0025A)
    - "An Evening of One-Act Plays and 2 Films", 3/1/87, 1987 (Folder ID: 192.0120)
    - "One-Acts and 2 Films", 2/22/87, 1987 (Folder ID: 192.0101)
    - "They Were Poor, But They Were Honest", Music Hall, 7/18/87, 1987 (Folder ID: 192.0023)
    - "Mixed Signals" Programs 1+2, Spring 1987; "Discovery of the Phonograph" w/ interview (Folder ID: 192.0103)
    - "The Yellow Chair" [play], 7/26/87, 1987 (Folder ID: 192.0107)
    - "They Were Poor, But They Were Honest", 7/17/87, 1987 (Folder ID: 192.0111)
    - "School of Jolly Dogs", 12/87, 1987 (Folder ID: 192.0112)
    - "Slant (Concerning Emily Sickinson)", 11/14/87, Hampshire College, 1987 (Folder ID: 192.0192)
    - "An Evening of Performance and Film" conceived and directed by Stuart Sherman, The Club, La MaMa 6/11/88, 1988 (Folder ID: 192.0009)
    - "An Evening of Performance and Film", La MaMa, 6/11/88, 1988 (Folder ID: 192.0090)
    - Central Park Performance, 9/11/88, 1988 (Folder ID: 192.0106)
    - "Berlin Tour" [film], 1988 (Folder ID: 192.0115)
      TRT: [00:12:00]
    - Battery Park performance, 9/12/88, 1988 (Folder ID: 192.0124)
    - "An Evening of Performance and Film", 6/9/88 (Tape 1 of 2), 1988 (Folder ID: 192.0130)
    - "An Evening of Performance and Film", 6/9/88 (Tape 2 of 2), 1988 (Folder ID: 192.0131)
    - "Bicycle", Cologne, [1988] (Folder ID: 192.0096)
    - "Sukiyaki a la Sherman a la Tokyo" and other acts, [1988] (Folder ID: 192.0097)
    - Dixon's Place 3/10/89, video by Taka Iimura, 1989 (Folder ID: 192.0021)
    - "Clocktower", 4/22/89, 1989 (Folder ID: 192.0050)
    - "Clocktower", "Vienna" 4/22/89, 1989 (Folder ID: 192.0122)
    - "Black-Eyed Susan (Portrait of An Actress)", 1989 (Folder 192.0144A)
    - "The Fourteenth Spectacle", 8/26/89, 1989 (Folder ID: 192.0161)
    - "Three Pieces", "Play of Tea", [1989] (Folder ID: 192.0180)
      Format: Video8
    - "Tea" (A intro), [1989] (Folder ID: 192.0142)
    - "Tea" (A), [1989] (Folder ID: 192.0188)
    - "Tea" (B), [1989] (Folder ID: 192.0075)
    - "Tea" (intro of B+C [?]), [1989] (Folder ID: 192.0127)
    - "Tea" (C), [1989] (Folder ID: 192.0145)
    - "Tea" (C), [1989] (Folder ID: 192.0181)
    - Tech rehearsal for play, late 80s, 198? (Folder ID: 192.0105)
    - "The Fifteenth Spectacle: Epoche", 6/23/90, 1990 (Folder ID: 192.0092)
    - "The Fifteenth Spectacle" [?], [1990] (Folder ID: 192.0121)
    - Artist Talk 9/14/90, 1990 (Folder ID: 192.0093)
    - "Aber Wie Heisst Das Wort For Fahrrad", Kolner Ensemble w/ Stuart, 1990 (Folder ID: 192.0113)
    - Video Mix, Whitney Museum, 11/25/90, 1990 (Folder ID: 192.0143)
    - "The Sixteenth Spectacle: A Musical", La MaMa, 3/18/91, 1991 (Folder ID: 192.0177)
    - New Langton, [1991] (Folder ID: 192.0024)
    - "The Fifteenth Spectacle", New Langton Arts (SF), [1991] (Folder ID: 192.0108)
    - Installation, "Video encyc.", New Langton [?], [1991] (Folder ID: 192.0109)
    - Tom and Stuart, Dixon Place, 10/10/92, 1992 (Folder ID: 192.0085)
    - "New Arts Alive" (BCTV), 9/8/92 (intro. James Carroll), 1992 (Folder ID: 192.0116)
    - Rutgers Tap Teaching Styles, 1993 (Folder ID: 192.0028)
    - "The Eighteenth Spectacle", 6/17/93, 1993 (Folder ID: 192.0043)
    - "Cheers!", 5/13/93, 1993 (Folder ID: 192.0049)
    - "The Eighteenth Spectacle", 6/17/93, 1993 (Folder ID: 192.0077)
    - "Pixil", Dixon Place, 9/14/93, 1993 (Folder ID: 192.0100)
    - "The Eighteenth Spectacle - Spaghetti Works", 6/12/93, 1993 (Folder ID: 192.0175)
    - 3/6/1993 (Folder ID: 192.0182)
    - Karaoke, 3/12/93, 1993 (Folder ID: 192.0183)
    - "Scaffolding", [1993] (Folder ID: 192.0110)
    - "A Glass of Fish", [1993] (Folder ID: 192.0045)
    - "The Leap" Dailies, [1993] (Folder ID: 192.0047)
    - "A Glass of Fish", [1993] (Folder ID: 192.0069)
    - Films/Video - "Don't Hang Up, I'm Freezing"; "A Glass of Fish"; "Cheers"; "2 Pixel Videos"; "The Leap"; "Son of Scotty and Stuart", [1993] (Folder ID: 192.0104)
    - "Liberation (Portrait of Berenice Reynaud)", [1993] (Folder ID: 192.0114)
    - "Liberation (Portrait of Berenice Reynaud)", [1993] (Folder ID: 192.0132)
    - "Son of Scotty and Stuart", [1993] (Folder ID: 192.0134)
    - "Cheers!" (#3), Titles for Tape (#1), 2 Pixel Videos (#4): "Black and White" and "Grain", [1993] (Folder ID: 192.0019)